Hey, how's it going?
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
So I'll switch over to the Gaza thing in a second, but first off, I just wanted to touch
on that.
You said that you support free speech, of course, right?
So what I'm confused about is you've refused to debate people that have disagreed with
you because you said that they're racist or they're fascist, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
If we're going to do facts, they said they were racist and fascist.
Get your facts right before you start arguing.
Okay.
So isn't the whole entire point of the debate to debate people that you don't agree with?
I don't debate people who don't see me, A, as equal, no point, or B, support democracy
because that would undermine the whole idea of the debate.
If you don't support democracy, as our friend here doesn't, and support General Franco,
then what is the point of a debate?
The First Amendment doesn't mean you have to debate everyone.
Somebody comes up to you in the street and starts talking to you, you don't have an obligation
to carry on talking to them.
I'm sure you go about your business.
Somebody comes up to you in the subway and sits next to you and starts ranting in your
face.
So you're not going to start debating.
So everyone here has hygiene standards, as do you.
There are people you wouldn't debate, I'm sure, as well.
Okay.
So can you please describe why you think Trump is supporting ethnic cleansing of Gaza just
because he wants to take over the land there?
How does that equate to killing them?
And not just take over the land.
Kick out all the people.
That is the definition of ethnic cleansing.
So isn't ethnic cleansing killing people?
Because it seems like you're-
No, you can ethnic cleanse people without killing them.
And by the way, they have been killed.
More than 50,000 people in Gaza have been killed by the Israelis, by people like Bezalel
Smotrich, who said recently, the finance minister of Israel, we are going to Gaza to conquer,
cleanse, and remain.
We are going to annihilate the place.
We are going to disassemble Gaza, he said.
We're going to leave it behind as piles of rubble.
That's the guy Trump's funding, supporting.
That's the guy praising Trump.
So yes, Trump and Smotrich are ethnically cleansing Gaza.
I cannot deny that thousands of people are dying in Gaza, but you need to realize, why
are they dying?
Is it possibly that they're attacking another country?
No.
The people who are dying, we're not attacking another country.
Just because Israel is killing more Gazans than Gazans are killing Israel doesn't mean
Gaza is righteous and Israel is evil.
Israel-
I never said anything about evil or righteous.
Israel might be-
I said ethnic cleansing.
You said, don't they have to be killed?
I said they are being killed.
And the criteria for what's happening to them.
If Donald Trump says, these people have to leave and never come back, is that not ethnic
cleansing?
What is your definition of ethnic cleansing?
Ethnic cleansing is when you're killing off a large part of an ethnic group.
That's genocide.
You're confusing your terms.
Ethnic cleansing is removing one ethnic group, using a deliberate policy by violence or terror
inspiring means to remove another population, another ethnic group from a certain geographic
area.
That's the UN definition of ethnic cleansing.
That is what he's doing.
When he was asked, Donald Trump, can they come back?
He said, no, they cannot.
That is ethnic cleansing.
I've heard all these-
We've had people talk about white genocides, and you guys are nationalists.
How would you feel if somebody came, a president of France came and told you to leave your
land and not come back?
Would you not feel you'd been ethnically cleansed from your home?
From America?
Yeah.
Well, because my ancestors were settlers here, not immigrants.
They actually built something-
Palestinians are not immigrants in Gaza.
They are indigenous people to the land.
Didn't Israel just give Gaza land a few decades ago?